online3fs.com 2010-02-05

# Fund management, Offshore Investment, Online Investment, Plan your retirement

The Internet is an amazing tool. It has the power to change the way we live, and we're starting to see that potential today. With only a few mouse-clicks, you can follow the news, look up facts, buy goods and services, and communicate with others from around the world. It's important to Online3FS  to help its customers retain their privacy when they take advantage of all the Internet has to offer. 

We believe your business is no one else's. Your privacy is important to you and to us. So we'll protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, Online3FS follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

q        We won’t sell or give away Investor's name, mail address, phone number, email address or any other information to anyone. 

q        We’ll use state-of-the-art security measures to protect your information from unauthorized users. 

**NOTICE**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you create a Registration ID on the site or when you file your bank account information. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

q        To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. 

q        To help you quickly find documents, services or information. 

q        To help us create content most relevant to you. 

q        To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from Online3FS. 

**CONSENT**

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of [www.Online3FS.com](https://www.online3fs.com/). But you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding Online3FS products, programs, events, or services by email, postal mail, or telephone, you may select the option stating that you do not wish to receive marketing messages from Online3FS. 

**ACCESS**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time at your "My Office". There, you can:

q        View and edit personal information you have already given us. 

q        Sign up for electronic newsletters about our services and products. You can contact us and request to unsubscribe from our newsletter service.

**SECURITY**

Online3FS Corp has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

We guarantee your e-commerce transactions to be 100% safe and secure. When you place orders or access your personal account information, you're utilizing secure server software SSL, which encrypts your personal information before it's sent over the Internet. SSL is one of the safest encryption technologies available.

Online3FS Corp strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in USA or any other country where Online3FS, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your Investor ID and password, Pin-Lock or Security Pin so do not share these with others.

**NOTICE TO PARENTS**

Parents or guardians: we want to help you guard your children's privacy. We encourage you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. The Online3FS site does not publish content that is targeted to children.

**ENFORCEMENT**

If for some reason you believe Online3FS has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by email at privacy@Online3FS.com, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

**CUSTOMER PROFILES**

As mentioned above, every registered customer has a unique personal profile. Each profile is assigned a unique personal identification number, which helps us ensure that only you can access your profile.

When you register, we create your profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your hard drive in the form of a cookie, which is a very small bit of code. This code is uniquely yours. It is your passport to seamless travel across [ www.Online3FS.com](https://www.online3fs.com/), allowing you to visit premium sites without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. Even if you switch computers, you won't have to re-register – just use your Investor ID to identify yourself. 

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE**

When you join us, you provide us with your contact information, including Investor's name and email address. We use this information to send you updates about your investment, questionnaires to measure your satisfaction with our service and announcements about new and exciting services that we offer. 

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Online3FS Corp will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Online3FS or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Online3FS Corp and its family of Websites, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Online3FS, its Websites, or the public.
